Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- RECORD GROUP B: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 202 SEATTLE, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-47/1, 69-73)
  - SERIES XI: CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS, 1892-1980 (Box-folder 26/1-41/22)
    - Flaig Appeal, 1938 (Box-folder 27/40)
    - Stivers Parrish, Glenn et al, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 27/41)
    - Gowler, A.W. vs Executive Committee Roy Gilmore Case, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 27/42)
    - W.L. McHale and Geo V. Hill vs J.L. Foley charges "Unpaid Wages", 1933 (Box-folder 27/43)
    - Charges- Executive Committee vs B.E. Goodrich "Ludington lease", 1932 (Box-folder 27/44)
    - Charges Seattle Typographical Union vs J.S. Winans "Ludington lease", 1932 (Box-folder 27/45)
    - Jessup, A.B. vs Graham, P.M. Charges, 1932 (Box-folder 27/46)
    - S.A. Serber vs. Seattle Typographical Union #202, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 27/47)
    - J.C. Krenz et al vs Post-Intelligencer Chapel (Stivers Case), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 27/48)
    - Appeal Reardon vs Times Chapel, Undated (Box-folder 27/49)
    - Wilcox-Vaughan Appeals, 1937 (Box-folder 27/50)
    - 75th Anniversary and Book, 1882-1959 (Box-folder 27/51)
    - Election Results 1967-1969 Local and International Typographical Union (Box-folder 27/52)
    - Referendums 1960-1969 (Box-folder 27/53)
    - Everett Herald 1958 #2 (Box-folder 27/54)
    - Everett Job Scale (Part 1), 1957 (Box-folder 27/55)
    - Everett Job Scale (Part 2), 1957 (Box-folder 27/56)
    - Everett Job Scale, 1956 (Box-folder 27/57)
    - Everett Job Scale #2, 1956 (Box-folder 27/58)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer, Times Signed Contracts, 1957 (Box-folder 27/59)
    - News Publishing Co., Journal of Commerce Signed Contracts, 1957 (Box-folder 27/60)
    - News Scale, 1954 (Box-folder 27/61)
    - News Scale, 1952 (Box-folder 27/62)
    - News Scale, 1953 (Box-folder 27/63)
    - News Scale, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 27/64)
    - Job Scale, 1952 (Box-folder 27/65)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer and Times Contracts, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 27/66)
    - Job Scale, 1950 (Box-folder 27/67)
    - Job Scale, 1949 (Box-folder 27/68)
    - News Scale, 1949 (Box-folder 27/69)
    - Strike (Newspaper) 1933 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer Strike 1924-25, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Textbook Committee, 1935-1939 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Job Lockout 1919 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Miscellaneous (includes a resignation letter, industrial code request letter, and request for union traveler card), 1953-1958 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Wage and Hour Division, State of Washington, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Environmental Research, State of Washington, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Washington Commonwealth Federation, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Washington State Conference of Typographical Unions 1941-1955 (Part 1), 1941-1956 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Washington State Conference of Typographical Unions 1941-1955 (Part 2), 1941-1956 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1931-1956 (Box-folder 28/11)
    - 1943 News Scale (Box-folder 28/12)
    - Apprenticeship Record Book, c. 1916-1952 (Box-folder 28/13)
    - 1944 News Scale, 1939-1945 (Box-folder 28/14)
    - 1945-6 Newspaper Scale (Strike) Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 28/15)
    - 1946-47 Newspaper Negotiations (Part 1), 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28/16)
    - 1946-47 Newspaper Negotiations (Part 2), 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28/17)
    - 1942 News Scale, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 28/18)
    - 1944 News #1 (Part 1), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 28/19)
    - 1944 News #1 (Part 2), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 28/20)
    - 1933 News Scale Arbitration, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 28/21)
    - 1944 Scale Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 28/22)
    - 1941 News Scale (Part 1), 1936-1941 (Box-folder 28/23)
    - 1941 News Scale (Part 2), 1936-1941 (Box-folder 28/24)
    - 1939 Arbitration (Box-folder 28/25)
    - Invoices, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 28/26)
    - 1937-38 News Scales, 1938 (Box-folder 28/27)
    - 1936 Guild Strikes and Lockout, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 28/28)
    - 1935 Arbitration, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 28/29)
    - 1934 News Scale Arbitration (Box-folder 28/30)
    - 1927 Seattle Post Intelligencer Arbitration, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 28/31)
    - 1963 Newspaper Negotiation Minutes (Box-folder 29/1)
    - 1963 Newspaper Contract Negotiations (Part 1) (Box-folder 29/2)
    - 1963 Newspaper Contract Negotiations (Part 2) (Box-folder 29/3)
    - 1963 Newspaper Scale Negotiations (Box-folder 29/4)
    - 1963 Contract Negotiations - R.L. Wartinger (Box-folder 29/5)
    - 1963 Contract Negotiations - Bill Titus (Box-folder 29/6)
    - 1963 Newspaper Proposal returned from International Typographical Union Contract Department (Box-folder 29/7)
    - 1963 Newspaper Contract Partial Agreement (Box-folder 29/8)
    - 1963 Newspaper Contract Partial Agreement and Final (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Seattle Commercial Contract (Part 1), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 29/10)
    - Seattle Commercial Contract (Part 2), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 29/11)
    - Seattle Job Scale #1 (Part 1), 1957-1959 (Box-folder 29/12)
    - Seattle Job Scale #1 (Part 2), 1957-1959 (Box-folder 29/13)
    - Everett Herald Contract 1960-1962 (Box-folder 29/14)
    - Everett Herald 1958 #1 (Part 1) (Box-folder 29/15)
    - Everett Herald 1958 #1 (Part 2) (Box-folder 29/16)
    - Seattle Job Scale #2 (Part 1), 1957 (Box-folder 29/17)
    - Seattle Job Scale #2 (Part 2), 1957 (Box-folder 29/18)
    - Seattle Job Scale #3 (Part 1), 1957 (Box-folder 29/19)
    - Seattle Job Scale #3 (Part 2), 1957 (Box-folder 29/20)
    - 1936 Arbitration (Part 1) (Box-folder 29/21)
    - 1936 Arbitration (Part 2), 1936-1941 (Box-folder 29/22)
    - 1955 Seattle Job Scale (Part 1), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 29/23)
    - 1955 Seattle Job Scale (Part 2), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 29/24)
    - 1944 National War Labor Board Job Scale Dispute (Box-folder 29/25)
    - Thornhill 1962-1964, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 29/26)
    - Thornhill 1963-1964 (Box-folder 29/27)
    - Everett Herald Scale 1960 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - 1968-1971 Trade Typesetting, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - 1956-1962 Mediation Notices and 60-day Notifications (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Highline-White Center Scale 1958, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - 1963-1966 Mediation Notices and 60-day Notifications (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Everett Herald 1964-1967 (Part 1), 1962-1964 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Everett Herald 1964-1967 (Part 2), 1962-1964 (Box-folder 30/7)
    - Everett Commercial 1964, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 30/8)
    - 1962 Highline-White Center, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - 1964 Thornhill (Box-folder 30/10)
    - 1962 Everett Commercial, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 30/11)
    - Printing Industry of Everett 1961 Negative and Copy, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 30/12)
    - 1961 Thornhill Scale (Box-folder 30/13)
    - 1959-1961 Seattle Newspaper Scale, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 30/14)
    - Times Correspondence through 1951, 1923-1951 (Box-folder 30/15)
    - 1959 Newspaper Contract Negotiation, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 30/16)
    - Printing Industry of Everett 1959, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 30/17)
    - 1957 Thornhill Printing Scale, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 30/18)
    - 1959 Seattle Commercial Scale (Part 1), 1957-1961 (Box-folder 30/19)
    - 1959 Seattle Commercial Scale (Part 2), 1957-1961 (Box-folder 30/20)
    - 1955 Seattle News Scale, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 30/21)
    - 1961 Everett Commercial Scale, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - 1966-69 Newspaper Negotiations (Part 1), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - 1966-69 Newspaper Negotiations (Part 2), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - 1966-68 News Publishing (Part 1), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - 1966-68 News Publishing (Part 2), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - 1962 Everett Herald (Part 1) (Box-folder 31/6)
    - 1962 Everett Herald (Part 2) (Box-folder 31/7)
    - 1968 Newspaper Contract Proposal (Box-folder 31/8)
    - AFL-CIO Newspaper, 1965 (Box-folder 31/9)
    - 1966 Newspaper Negotiations, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - 1966 Newspaper Negotiations Info-Minutes, etc. (Part 1) (Box-folder 31/11)
    - 1966 Newspaper Negotiations Info-Minutes, etc. (Part 2) (Box-folder 31/12)
    - Newspaper Contracts 1954-1968 Jurisdiction Section, 1954-1966 (Box-folder 31/13)
    - Renton Chapel Records, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 31/14)
    - Record-Chronicle, 1964 (Box-folder 31/15)
    - 110 Years Plus of Democratic Trade Unionism, 1962 (Box-folder 31/16)
    - Welfare and Pension Info (Part 1), 1951-1965 (Box-folder 31/17)
    - Welfare and Pension Info (Part 2), 1951-1965 (Box-folder 31/18)
    - 1967-1969 Everett Commercial (Part 1), 1967-1972 (Box-folder 31/19)
    - 1967-1969 Everett Commercial (Part 2), 1967-1972 (Box-folder 31/20)
    - 1969 111th International Typographical Union Convention - Communications (Part 1), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 31/21)
    - 1969 111th International Typographical Union Convention - Communications (Part 2), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 31/22)
    - 1969 111 International Typographical Union Convention - Banquet Fare, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 31/23)
    - 1969 111th International Typographical Union Convention - Banquet Menu and Programs, 1957-1969 (Box-folder 31/24)
    - Repro Proof Committee News Contract, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Seattle News Scale #1, 1957 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Seattle News Scale #2, 1957 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - 1959 Thornhill Printing Company Scale (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Employer Pension Plan, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - 1966-69 West Seattle, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Renton-Bellevue Bogle, Bogle, and Gates - Jackson, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Secretary Willard Olson (Part 1), 1961-1965 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Secretary Willard Olson (Part 2), 1961-1965 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Secretary Willard Olson (Part 3) - Typographical Mutual Aid Fund, 1953-1964 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - 1963 Commercial Craftsman Press Metropolitan Press (Part 1), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 32/11)
    - 1963 Commercial Craftsman Press Metropolitan Press (Part 2), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - 1963 Commercial Craftsman Press Metropolitan Press (Part 3), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Scott Publishing Company vs. Columbia Basin News (Part 1), 1958 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Scott Publishing Company vs. Columbia Basin News (Part 2), 1949-1959 (Box-folder 32/15)
    - 1963 News Negotiations - Letters, Etc. (Part 1) (Box-folder 32/16)
    - 1963 News Negotiations - Letters, Etc. (Part 2), 1959-1964 (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Correspondence and Wage Rates, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Automation Seminar, 1972 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Apprentice Committee, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - North Central Outlook, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Printing Industry - State Law, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - University of Washington Proposals, 1969 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - University of Washington Negotiations, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Trade Typesetting, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Pacifictype, 1971 (Box-folder 33/9)
    - University of Washington Negotiations- Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - 1969 Everett Herald Negotiations, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 33/11)
    - University of Washington Bert Hagg, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 33/12)
    - 1968 Everett Herald Negotiations, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 33/13)
    - 1969 University of Washington Negotiations (Part 1), 1957-1969 (Box-folder 33/14)
    - 1969 University of Washington Negotiations (Part 2), 1957-1969 (Box-folder 33/15)
    - University of Washington Copies of Proposals, 1968 (Box-folder 33/16)
    - Outside Tape, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 33/17)
    - Washington Law Review, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 33/18)
    - University of Washington - Miscellaneous, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 33/19)
    - IRS Pay Board, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 33/20)
    - ITU Pension, 1968 (Box-folder 33/21)
    - STU - ITU Pension (Part 1), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 33/22)
    - STU - ITU Pension (Part 2), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 33/23)
    - STU - ITU Pension (Part 3), 1968-1969 (Box-folder 33/24)
    - Trustee - Life and Disability (Part 1), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 33/25)
    - Trustee - Life and Disability (Part 2), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 33/26)
    - Washington State Labor Council 1965 State Convention (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Seattle Typographical Union - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Allied Printers, 1939-1955 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - 1971 Craftsman - Metropolitan Press (Box-folder 34/4)
    - 1961-1970 Craftsman - Metropolitan Press, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 34/5)
    - 1938-1960 Craftsman - Metropolitan Press (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Craftsman - LandH - Metropolitan Press, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Everett Herald, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Frayn Printing, 1931-1974 (Box-folder 34/9)
    - Grange Lockout 1978 (Box-folder 34/10)
    - Grange Co-Op, 1939-1976 (Box-folder 34/11)
    - Journal of Commerce, 1928-1976 (Box-folder 34/12)
    - Klovee, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34/13)
    - Labor Advocate, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 34/14)
    - Pacifictype, Inc., 1942-1978 (Box-folder 34/15)
    - Post-Intelligencer #1 (Part 1), 1958-1977 (Box-folder 34/16)
    - Post-Intelligencer #1 (Part 2), 1958-1977 (Box-folder 34/17)
    - Post-Intelligencer #2, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 34/18)
    - Post-Intelligencer Machinists, 1972 (Box-folder 34/19)
    - Seattle Times #1 (Part 1), 1930-1976 (Box-folder 34/20)
    - Seattle Times #1 (Part 2), 1930-1976 (Box-folder 34/21)
    - Tacoma News Tribune, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 34/22)
    - University of Washington #1 (Part 1), 1929-1977 (Box-folder 34/23)
    - University of Washington #1 (Part 2), 1929-1977 (Box-folder 34/24)
    - National Labor Relations Board State Case vs University of Washington, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 34/25)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Employers Plan Pension (Part 1), 1960-1971 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Employers Plan Pension (Part 2), 1960-1971 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Employers Plan Pension (Part 3), 1960-1971 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - 1968-1971 News Publishing Negotiations (Box-folder 35/4)
    - 1968-1970 Seattle News (Part 1), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - 1968-1970 Seattle News (Part 2), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Citizens' Job Protection Law Kit, Undated (Box-folder 35/7)
    - Secretaries - Talbot, Goodwyn, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 35/8)
    - Winnipeg Citizen - National War Labor Board, 1943-1947 (Box-folder 35/9)
    - 1964-1966 Highline-White Center; 1965-1966 Mid-City Publishing Company (Part 1), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 35/10)
    - 1964-1966 Highline-White Center; 1965-1966 Mid-City Publishing Company (Part 2), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 35/11)
    - President Cavanagh, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 35/12)
    - Fairchild - Teletypesetter (TTS), 1949-1965 (Box-folder 35/13)
    - 1968 Commercial Agreement, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 35/14)
    - 1966-1968 Commercial Contract (Part 1), 1964-1967 (Box-folder 35/15)
    - 1966-1968 Commercial Contract (Part 2), 1964-1967 (Box-folder 35/16)
    - 1967-1969 Everett Herald, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 35/17)
    - Seattle Newspaper Publishers' Association Negotiations - Scanner, 1974 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Post-Intelligencer Promotional Department, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - Seattle Times Incentives - Seattle Newspaper Publishers' Association, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 36/3)
    - Post-Intelligencer Joint Standing Committee 30 Day Situation, 1976 (Box-folder 36/4)
    - Warren's Quick Print, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36/5)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Everett Herald Arvidson Joint Standing Committee, 1977 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Daily Olympian and Downtown Contract Correspondence, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 36/8)
    - Daily News, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 36/9)
    - State Printing Plan 1975 Negotiations (Part 1), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 36/10)
    - State Printing Plan 1975 Negotiations (Part 2), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 36/11)
    - Vancouver Pensions, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 36/12)
    - Tacoma Commercial, 1976 (Box-folder 36/13)
    - Scanner Agreements, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 36/14)
    - Scanner Agreements New, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 36/15)
    - Optical Character Recognition (OCR) and Video Display Terminal (VDT) Information, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 36/16)
    - Olympia, 1974 (Box-folder 36/17)
    - Negotiations Data - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 36/18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box-folder 36/19)
    - Print New York, Undated (Box-folder 36/20)
    - 1974-75 University of Washington Department of Printing, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 36/21)
    - University of Washington Agreement, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 36/22)
    - University of Washington, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 36/23)
    - University of Washington - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 36/24)
    - Craftsman Press - TV Guide, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 36/25)
    - Craftsman Contract, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 36/26)
    - 1974 Cost of Living Information and Payboard, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 36/27)
    - Payboard - Commercial, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 36/28)
    - Craftsman Press Composing Room, 1956-1972 (Box-folder 36/29)
    - News Publishing, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 36/30)
    - 1974 News Publishing - Closing of Composition Room, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 36/31)
    - Washington State Conference of Typographical Unions, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 36/32)
    - University of Washington, 1946-1967 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Daily Herald, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Apprentice New Membership, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - TV Guide Supplemental Agreement, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Affirmative Action, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Bellingham, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Commercial - Printing Industry, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Craftsman Contract, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Craftsman Press, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 37/9)
    - Cursillo - Christian Community In Action (includes 3 photographs), 1971-1975 (Box-folder 37/10)
    - Craftsman Press, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 37/11)
    - Daily Journal of Commerce, 1976 (Box-folder 37/12)
    - Everett Herald, 1975 (Box-folder 37/13)
    - Everett Herald Negotiations 1971, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 37/14)
    - Everett Herald, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 37/15)
    - 1975 Everett Herald (Part 1), 1972-1975 (Box-folder 37/16)
    - 1975 Everett Herald (Part 2), 1972-1975 (Box-folder 37/17)
    - Miscellaneous Medical Plans, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 37/18)
    - Negotiation Data, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 37/19)
    - Art Foto, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Laws Changes, 1969 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Trick and Murray - Organization and Allied, 1963 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - 1968 Newspaper Negotiations (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Merger - General, 1974 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - President (Law Changes), 1976 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - International Typographical Union Pension Committee, 1976 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Pension Seminar, 1976 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Reproduction Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - Laws Committee #1, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - Laws Committee #2, 1976 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Committee on Local Union Merger, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 38/12)
    - Seattle Times Substitution Hire Joint Steering Committee, 1976 (Box-folder 38/13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box-folder 38/14)
    - Wage-Price Freeze, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 38/15)
    - Health and Welfare Insurance Plan, 1974 (Box-folder 38/16)
    - Pay Board, 1971 (Box-folder 38/17)
    - Tacoma, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 38/18)
    - Negotiated Pension Plan, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 38/19)
    - International Typographical Union Negotiated Pension Plan, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 38/20)
    - Union Printers' Home, 1949-1972 (Box-folder 38/21)
    - International Typographical Union Training Center, 1967 (Box-folder 38/22)
    - Apprentice Membership Forms, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 38/23)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1969 (Box-folder 38/24)
    - Washington State Conference of Typographical Unions, 1955-1974 (Box-folder 38/25)
    - Protest Byrotses, 1968 (Box-folder 38/26)
    - Communications - Bellingham Herald and Local Commercial Shops, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 38/27)
    - Seattle Pension Plan, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 38/28)
    - Committee on Political Education, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 38/29)
    - Bellingham Central Labor Council, 1952-1969 (Box-folder 38/30)
    - Newman - Burroughs, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - News Publishing Company, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Northwest Printing and Related Trades Conference, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Organization, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Organization #2, 1974 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Act - Washington Industrial Safety and Health Act, 1973 (Box-folder 39/6)
    - John Vandevanter Publication Services, 1975 (Box-folder 39/7)
    - Payboard, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 39/8)
    - Seattle Tyographical Union, No. 202 Financial Statement, May 31, 1972 and an American Management Association mailer (Box-folder 39/9)
    - School Training Center, 1971 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - Human Resources Manpower and Veterans Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 39/11)
    - Arbitration, Etc., 1969-1975 (Box-folder 39/12)
    - Citizens' Job Protection Law Kit and Higher Education Personnel Board Meeting and Agenda, March 31, 1971, 1960-1971 (Box-folder 39/13)
    - Los Angeles Herald-Examiner Strike, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 39/14)
    - Northwest Catholic Progress, 1971 (Box-folder 39/15)
    - Everett Herald - Negotiations - Burnett, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 39/16)
    - Miscellaneous (includes Post-Intelligencer meeting notes, Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association Agreement, typographers apprenticeship standards, Commercial Contract between Printing Industry of Seattle, Inc. and Seattle Typographical Union, No. 202), 1969-1975 (Box-folder 39/17)
    - Bremerton Composing Room, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/18)
    - Bremerton Commercial Contract, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 39/19)
    - Advisory Committee Duties, 1974 (Box-folder 39/20)
    - Convention Bureau, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 39/21)
    - Memorandum Agreements Between Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association, as Representative of the Seattle Times Company, and Seattle Typographical Union Local No. 202, 1961-1971 (Box-folder 39/22)
    - Book Publishing Company Negotiations - Frayne, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/23)
    - State Printing Plant Contracts, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 39/24)
    - Optometry Plan, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/25)
    - Highline, 1975 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Minorities - Human Relations Commission, 1974 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - Longview, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Longview - General, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Daily Olympia, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Daily Olympia #2, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Daily Olypmpia #3, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Portland Scribe, 1975 (Box-folder 40/8)
    - Post-Intelligencer, 1976 (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Pierce County Herald, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 40/10)
    - Rybnikar, Robert, 1975 (Box-folder 40/11)
    - Seattle Commercial, 1974 (Box-folder 40/12)
    - Schwarz, Charles, 1975 (Box-folder 40/13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box-folder 40/14)
    - Tacoma News Tribune Joint Steering Committee: Machinists, 1975 (Box-folder 40/15)
    - Tacoma News Tribune, 1974 (Box-folder 40/16)
    - Camera 1975, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 40/17)
    - Tacoma News Tribune 1972 Camera, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 40/18)
    - Tacoma News Tribune Television Log, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 40/19)
    - Tacoma News Tribune Miscellaneous, 1976-1976 (Box-folder 40/20)
    - 1973-74 Trade Typesetting (Part 1), 1975-1980 (Box-folder 40/21)
    - 1973-74 Trade Typesetting (Part 2), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 40/22)
    - Vancouver, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 40/23)
    - Vancouver #2, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40/24)
    - Vancouver Columbian Editorial, 1975 (Box-folder 40/25)
    - Vancouver #3, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 40/26)